At the same place.
How many are these sky people?
Hello. I'm Yuki Yoda.
My name is Yuki Yoda. I'm here today at the Satsukiyama Zoo.
Today we are here at the Satsukiyama Zoo, where my favorite animal, the wombat, lives.
I'm so happy! I'm so nervous, I'm so nervous!
I'm a little nervous! I brought two cameras!
Wombats are my first love in life!
So I went to the hairdresser yesterday to meet my guess.
I'm so excited.
So cute! I don't remember seeing so many sheep.
Hey, hey...
I was the loudest.
It's like waiting in line for an event.
The thrill of excitement.
"My guesses are getting closer..." "My guesses are getting closer...
I wonder if it's okay... the bangs...
I'll ring the goats first, too.
I'm sorry.
Hey, goat!
It's coming! Oh, here it comes.
Meh.
I don't get it.
You're so quiet.
It's so quiet.
Bye-bye.
I'm hiring.
I've been watching the live stream on youtube, but I don't sleep well.
But he sleeps a lot. He's not here.
He's sleeping.
Wait a minute.
He's sleeping so much.
Too cute!
I can't do it! Wait a minute!
What's with the sleeping face?
His mouth is half open.
He's sleeping with his mouth half open.
Let's take a picture with my phone.
Oh, man.
He's cute.
Today...
The second smallest zoo in Japan
And my favorite zoo in Japan
I'm meeting the director of my favorite zoo in Japan.
I'm meeting him right now.
I'm meeting him now.
Um...
How do you do?
It's nice to meet you.
Yes, it's nice to meet you.
I've been sneaking up on you.
I've been watching you.
Thank you very much.
I love you, Bombot.
This is my favorite part.
Okay, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad you like it.
I'm going to be in charge.
It's my dream.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'd love to work there someday.
I'd love to try it sometime.
Is that okay?
I'd really like to.
I'm close to a friend.
Not for a day, not for a month, not at all.
I'd love to. I'd love to.
Please come.
I look forward to working with you.
Hey.
I think I'm going to get a great job.
Thank you very much.
I'm so glad.
You should try it. It's fun.
Are you sure?
Yes, let's go in.
I'm so nervous.
I never thought I'd be in a place like this.
I never dreamed I'd be in a place like this.
Are you all right?
Thank you. I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I don't know if this is a good idea.
So this is how it's supposed to be.
Yes, it is.
Like this.
Like this... they're cooking food...
Here.
Yes, sir.
Cooking food
Yes, too.
Oh, wow.
That's exciting.
of my notice that wasn't there earlier.
Fuku-kun.
Are you there?
I'm sorry to bother you.
No, it's okay.
Excuse me.
He's so cute.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm taking a break.
I just woke up. I think I just woke up.
"Fukkun!
I said "boohoo".
"Fukkun.
He's so cute!
Oh, here he comes!
Here it comes... here it comes...
If it's around the head...
Around the head.
I'll go.
What?
I don't care if you rip my fingers off.
I'm so happy!
He's so cute!
What shall I do?
Wow!
I'm glad I tried so hard.
desposito
Fuku-kun
Oh no!
It's like when I'm at a handshake event or something, and the fans are kind of crying.
I'm feeling that feeling. I'm about to cry.
I'm so happy to be able to meet my guesses
Oh no! I just had a nightmare!
I'll feed him.
Are you sure?
Thank you very much.
I'll have him hold the tree.
Yes, sir.
The leaf part.
Yes.
Would you like some?
I'll bring it to you on a skewer.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
It's so cute!
Delicious!
I feel like I'm going to start sniffling if I try to hold back my tears.
Oh, no.
Close your eyes.
I can't stop looking at it.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Your hips are so hard, aren't they?
Yes, it's hard.
Muscles and this and that.
It's very strong.
It's like a hip attack weapon.
Yes, hip attack.
He also has a hard head.
That's right.
Yes, sir
Yes, sir.
Face.
I just saw your face.
I just looked up.
Okay, follow me.
Oh, nice.
Oh, my God.
I don't know if I want to be kept here.
I'd rather be kept here.
I'd rather...
It's rare that they squeak.
It's true, my eyes are watery.
I'm trying to hold it in, but I'm afraid it'll turn into a sniffle.
I don't know, but I've never heard you squeal here before.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
It's a little embarrassing.
He's holding back a lot.
What's your personality like?
I'm...
I'm not very conscious.
I'm strong-willed.
I can be sweet when I want to be.
Tsunbere.
That's right.
I have a weakness for tsunbere.
Do you remember her name?
Well, I don't blow her name clearly.
I react to them by imitating their crying.
Like a crying imitation.
Like "shu-shu-shu-shu".
Shoo-shoo-shoo.
Like a pico.
Shu-shu-shu-shu.
Cute, you're drawing.
You also draw butts, don't you?
Yes, I do draw butts.
That's so cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
Yah!
Ya, I can touch her butt.
Oh!
He's digging so hard.
I can't believe it feels like that.
What does it look like?
Just like I imagined.
Oh, my God.
Maybe I'll come back tomorrow.
Oh, God, I can't go home.
I don't want to go home.
Do I have to?
Maybe there's a way to survive here.
Why is he in the top corner?
I love his face.
I really like the way he draws the face and the butt.
And there's a video of him grinding his butt.
It's something that comes on a lot.
I started to like it.
He's so cute.
There's Mr. Wine.
Mr. Wine is...
He's a Guinness World Record holder.
34 years old.
He's the world's longest living man.
Grandfather.
Wow!
He's a great teacher of wine.
And Mr. Yuki.
Mr. Yuki.
Hi.
Yuki-san, 23 years old.
Mr. Wine is 34.
I knew it. He's not the same. He's losing. Not at all.
When I came here a long time ago, just before I left, Mr. Wine came out to greet me and I was so happy to see him for a moment.
I was so happy.
Shoo-shoo-shoo.
He's responding.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Shoo-shoo-shoo!
You have a very unique way of moving.
Oh! I wonder if Mr. Yuki, now that he's a little wombat, will be here.
Hey there.
I've been reborn.
I think we're friends now. I think we've gone from one-sided acquaintances to friends. I want to take a picture of you with your best bangs.
Oh, back, back, back...
Shoo-shoo-shoo!
Shuffle, shuffle, shuffle.
Yes, I did it!
I got a huge back kick!
I got so much back.
It's okay, but...
Shoo, shoo, shoo, shoo...
Shoo, shoo, shoo, shoo.
Shoo-shoo-shoo.
I'm up!
Kuch.
CherryT lee
What an interesting creature!
So cute.
I'm off.
Embarrassing. Wait, more embarrassing than I thought. More embarrassing than I thought.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm so embarrassed. I'm so embarrassed.
I'm so embarrassed.
Oh, we're back together now!
I'm so embarrassed that we're in front of the audience together.
We're on the same team now.
I'm a bombad.
But I'm still embarrassed... so I haven't become a full-fledged bombatt yet.
I'll work on it from now on.
My goal is to eventually become a Bombat.
How did you feel when you met Bombat?
I was so happy that I started to run my nose when I tried to hold back my tears.
But it was a very happy time.
I don't want to go home.
I don't want to leave, but I have to go home.
I'll see you again.
Nice to meet you
That's how I felt.
Thank you very much.
See you next time.
Seino
Please subscribe to our channel!
Bonbat ice cream!
Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
Oh, it's good, it's good, it's good.
Tastes even better because it's Bombat.
Yeah, this is mine.
My first pressed pork cutlet.
Is this how you feel about being awesome in life? Try to find a guess.
No, Yuki is fine.
What are you talking about?